let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 41,
    "question": "Mesodebris in the context of plastic debris has fragments of size",
    "answer": "5-20mm",
    "options": [">20mm", "5-20mm", "<5mm", "<1mm"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 42,
    "question": "The government came up with a regulation that incandescent bulbs be replaced by LED bulbs, so that electricity consumption and release of carbon dioxide from power plants is reduced. In the context change, such an action would be called",
    "answer": "mitigation",
    "options": ["adaptation", "mitigation", "deceleration", "maladaptation"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 43,
    "question": "Which of these is not a climatic forcing for Earth?",
    "answer": "changes in moon's orbit",
    "options": ["changes in plate tectonics", "changes in earth's orbit", "changes in moon's orbit", "changes in sun's orbit"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 44,
    "question": "Which of these is not a principle of ecological restoration",
    "answer": "benefits and engages scientists",
    "options": ["ecological integrity", "long-term sustainability", "benefits and engages scientists", "informed by past and future"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 45,
    "question": "\"The ability of a system to adjust to climate change (including climate variability and extremes) to moderate potential damages, to take advantage of opportunities, or to cope with the consequences\" is a definition for",
    "answer": "adaptive capacity",
    "options": ["adaptive response", "adaptive capacity", "mitigative response", "mitigative capacity"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 46,
    "question": "Which of these is not a principle of ecological restoration",
    "answer": "short-term sustainability",
    "options": ["ecological integrity", "short-term sustainability", "benefits and engages society", "informed by past and future"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 47,
    "question": "Macrodebris in context of plastic debris has fragments of size",
    "answer": ">20mm",
    "options": [">20mm", "5-20mm", "<5mm", "<1mm"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 48,
    "question": "Because of climate change, Mudumalai tiger reserve is suffering from frequent droughts. The management has built several artificial water holes for animals, and fills them up regularly with tankers. In the context of climate change, such an action would be called",
    "answer": "adaptation",
    "options": ["adaptation", "mitigation", "deceleration", "maladaptation"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 49,
    "question": "\"Any changes in natural and human systems that inadvertently increase vulnerability to climatic stimuli; an adaptation that does not succeed in reducing vulnerability but increases it instead\" is a definition for",
    "answer": "maladaptation",
    "options": ["adaptation", "mitigation", "maladaptation", "malmitigation"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 50,
    "question": "Which of these is not a climatic forcing for Earth",
    "answer": "changes in sun's orbit",
    "options": ["changes in plate tectonics", "changes in earth's orbit", "changes in sun's orbit", "changes in sun's strength"]
  }
]